<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Musings and Perusings</title>
    <description>Welcome! Francis here. I&#39;m a concert-chasing, coffee-obsessed, life-loving person just trying to make cool things and revolutionize education. Always down and trying to explore, adventure and experience. Senior | Informatics 2015 | UW | UX/UI/Industrial Design | Web Development</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 14:19:29 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 14:19:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blurriness</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My own personal break has concluded, signaling my ascent into the academic school year. Many of us experience relief, as probing, yet stock questions concerning the fall quarter come to a close. Others, revel in the social opportunities that await. And still others dread the advent of a fresh round of classes and over-eager professors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;College. The ephemeral journey into adulthood. A short, or not so short, 4 years dedicated to growth, learning, revelry, brotherhood, carnal pursuits, and “getting a job”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 months of eye-opening, uncomfortable, awkward, exhausting, exciting, and invigorating experiences that passed in a eternal blink of the eye. In hindsight, the first quarterexists in such a molding way that I am nearly incapable of recalling it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blur of life renders the full scope inscrutable. I gape at the speed with which entire months gallop into the past. Consider the gravity which a day holds. The day is momentous because of it’s banality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As students, our senses become deadened by routine. We live for the weekends and time away from schoolwork. The days pass in a prosaic blur, the journey into adulthood. Soon, adulthood loses its’ luster and passes in a similar blur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I long to embrace the uncomfortable. Revel in time spent with friends. And dispel overt worry from my life. But is that really enough? Time will tell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And maybe, just maybe, the blur will slow down.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 05:34:05 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/intro/writing/blog/2014/11/03/blurriness/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/intro/writing/blog/2014/11/03/blurriness/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>writing</category>
        
        
        <category>intro</category>
        
        <category>writing</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve finally put together enough things on GitHub to host a site and use Jekyll. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an attempt to cater to the writer in me, I’m going to attempt to update this every so often.
Drop by when I’ve updated it quite a bit more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Francis&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 05:20:05 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/intro/writing/blog/2014/11/03/welcome/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/intro/writing/blog/2014/11/03/welcome/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>beginning</category>
        
        
        <category>intro</category>
        
        <category>writing</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
